Being together is what makes a perfect Christmas.
Barbie: A Perfect Christmas is a animation, family film directed by Mark Baldo.
The vacation plans of Barbie and her sisters take a turn due to a snowstorm.
Stranded in Tannenbaum town, they find themselves amidst a holiday
venture where they learn a heartwarming lesson.
Barbie (voice), played by Diana Kaarina.
Barbie (singing voice), played by Jennifer Waris.
Skipper (voice), played by Rachel Drance.
Skipper (singing voice), played by Nevada Brandt.
Stacie (voice), played by Lauren Lavoie.
Stacie (singing voice), played by Danielle Bessler.
Barbie, a fashion doll manufactured by American toy and entertainment company Mattel, has starred or featured in 44 CGI-animated
feature films and streaming television films since 2001, which has become a core component of an eponymous media franchise.
In response to a growing rise of digital and interactive media as well as the gradual decline of the sales in Barbie dolls, toys and accessories in the 1980s, Mattel collaborated with animation studios to produce films which were broadcast on Nickelodeon in the United
States from 2002 to 2017 and released on home video formats, originally by Artisan Entertainment's home video division and Family Home Entertainment and their successor Lionsgate until 2006 and Universal Pictures Home Entertainment thereafter until 2017.
Since 2012, Mattel expanded the franchise beyond just the films to other audiovisual media such as web series, television shows and
streaming television content, with the latter following the growing trend of streaming services and online platforms.
In 2020, Mattel revamped the films into streaming television films, branding them as animated "specials" and integrating them
into the canon of the inaugural television show in the "Barbie" media franchise, Barbie: Dreamhouse Adventures.
A 2023 live-action film featuring the character and toyline
was theatrically released by Warner Bros.
and Mattel Films, alongside LuckyChap Entertainment and Heyday Films.
It released alongside Oppenheimer from Universal Pictures as one half of a suggested double-feature phenomenon named Barbenheimer and broke
numerous box-office records that year with a global gross of $ 1.44 billion, including the highest-grossing Warner Bros.-released film.
The film explores themes of based on toy, female
protagonist, christmas, 3d animation.
The tone is uplifting.